thenatureanimals.com 2011-06-05

# Privacy Policy | The Nature Animals

**The Nature Animals** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Personal Information**

We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. The Nature Animals is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
